1,You are ugly
1,You are stupid
1,You are worthless
1,You are not cool
1,You are a loser
1,You are a jerk
1,you are an ass
1,you are an ass hole
1,Kristen Stewart is the worst actress ever!
1,your face is so stupid I hate you
1,What the fuck is up with Amy Poehler√ïs face? Bitch looks like she survived a nuclear blast
1,If I had to choose between fucking a pie or Jason Biggs  I√ïd choose the pie. That dude has a dirty dick.
1,I hate you
1,Go kill yourself
1,kill yourself
1,jump off a bridge
1,you are gay
1,eat a bag of dicks
1,go jump off a cliff
1,you are dumb
1,you aren't cool
1,you are not cool
1,you are so stupid
1,don't be so stupid
1,why are you so stupid
1,why aren't you cool
1,why are you such a loser
1,why are you such a jerk
1,don't be such a loser
1,don't be such a jerk
1,you were born a loser
1,quit being such a loser
-1,you are nice
-1,I like you
-1,thanks for being nice
-1,want to go to the park?
-1,let's play
-1,thank you
-1,you are my friend
-1,In Food Court  we're all the judge.
-1,Yesterday  my sister & I visited a spirit medium; a spiritual experience in more ways than one. One will do anything to cope with real loss.
-1,An average donation of $37 with more than 400 000 donors√ëthis is a real grassroots movement: http://ofa.bo/iv√ä #OFAYearOne
-1,Toy Story' Starring Cats: To Kitten-finity and Beyond! [VIDEO]
-1,Speaking at @CoderDay with @nrrrdcore today! Excited to encourage participation in open source and helping non-profits  like @khanacademy!
-1,And now the question is *which* Chris Christie scandal is your favorite?
-1,Did you hear about the rodents accidentally cooked into the peach cobbler in Turks and Caicos? The Pie-Rats of the Caribbean I'm so sorry
-1,Soccer (football) experts: If an attacker w/ball gets past the last defender and then passes to a teammate (also past)  is it offsides?
-1,Of course  the best scam Christie ever pulled was convincing adults he was a moderate.
-1,One of the successes of my life is aiding my sister in her decision to keep her hair very long.
-1,How a giggly teenager rakes in $500K a year with shopping videos
-1,No topiary labyrinth is complete without a wayward toddler frantically screaming at the utter futility of the endeavor.
-1,Wars shatter so many lives. I think especially of children robbed of their childhood.
-1,Yo
-1,I like The Used - but mostly circa 2003.
-1,Motorola Cuts Moto X√ïs Wood Finishes From $100 to $25:
-1,Apple and Samsung Widen Lead in U.S. Phone Market
-1,Antennas Direct C4-CJM 20 ClearStream 4 Extreme Range Indoor/Outdoor UHF HDTV Antenna $23 + Free Shipping
-1,Durant could go for 60. This is nutty. #efficient
-1,Georgia Dabritz posts 9.95 on floor  9.9s on vault and uneven bars
-1,Headed into final rotation  Utes led 148.3-147.15 over Cal in gymnastics.
-1,I'll be honest  if society allowed it  I'd wear nothing but sweat pants.
-1,Sundance day 1: two awesome movies √ë God√ïs Pocket and Laggies. I AM INSPIRED